(
"ai_sub_version": "3.3.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-19T22:41:02.336298",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
※この配信は演出により激しく点滅する場面がございます。部屋を明るくし、画面から十分離れてご視聴ください。
*This broadcast contains scenes with intense flashing lights. Please watch in a well-lit room and stay a safe distance from the screen.
店長 兎田
[Manager Usada]
周年記念
[Anniversary Commemoration]
朝礼
[Morning Assembly]
まもなく！
[Coming Soon!]
さあ いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Step right up! Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
さあ いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Step right up! Welcome! Welcome!
本日はお忙しい中 数ある配信の中から当配信
Today, despite your busy schedules, out of all the streams...
兎田ぺこら7周年ライブをお選びいただき ご閲覧いただき 誠にありがとうございます！
thank you so much for choosing to watch Usada Pekora's 7th Anniversary Live!
日頃のご愛顧にお応えいたしまして
In return for your continued support,
兎田ぺこらオリジナルのステージを取り揃えましてのお出迎え
we welcome you with a custom-made Usada Pekora stage
お祭り騒ぎでゲストもたくさんでお送りいたします！
and bring you a festive show with lots of guests!
玉の方も メダルの方も すべて超・超・超おすすめでのお出迎えとなっておりますれば
Since both our pachinko balls and medals are highly, highly recommended...
どちらのお客様も 最後までじゃんじゃんバリバリとお楽しみくださいませ！
dear customers, please enjoy yourselves to the absolute fullest until the very end!
日頃ご自慢の右手左手に より一層の磨きをかけましてで
Put an even finer polish on your proud right and left hands,
しっかりとがっちりとコメントもしてくださいませ！
and make sure to leave plenty of comments!
さあ いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Step right up! Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Step right up! Welcome, welcome, welcome!
本日も様々な景品、グッズをご用意しております！
We have prepared various prizes and merchandise today as well!
ぜひ本日のライブの思い出に、おひとついかがでしょうか？
How about getting one as a memento of today's live concert?
1つ目の目玉商品は、こちら！
Our first featured item is this!
アクリルパネル！
The acrylic panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishのイナちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
This was actually drawn by Ina-chan from hololive English!
とってもレア、とってもレア、そして
It's extremely rare, very rare, and...
可愛いぺこらをありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
thank you so much for drawing such a cute Pekora!
イナ、ありがとう、イナ！
Ina, thank you, Ina!
ぜひとも皆様のデスクトップの隣に置くといいぺこですね。
It would look great right next to your computer desktop!
2つ目は、こちら！
Our second item is this!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Random acrylic keychains!
イラストは、まさえり先生に描いてもらいました！
The illustrations were drawn by Masaeri-sensei!
めちゃめちゃ可愛いぺこですね。
They are super-duper cute!
ぜひとも全部揃えたくなってしまう、そんなランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
You'll definitely want to collect them all, this random acrylic keychain set!
どれが来るかは届いてからのお楽しみぺこです！
You'll have to wait until they arrive to see which one you got!
3つ目は、
The third item is...
ぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
the \"You've gotta be kidding me...\" T-shirt handwritten by Pekora!
この暑い夏を乗り切るのにぴったりなTシャツ！
It's the perfect T-shirt to get through this hot summer!
「うそぺこでしょ…」の出番がきっとある！そんな時に着たいTシャツぺこですね！
There will surely be moments to say \"You've gotta be kidding me...\"! That's when you should wear it!
4つ目は、トラックジャケット！
The fourth item is the track jacket!
こちらもまた最高にカッコいいぺこですね！
This is also incredibly cool!
後ろにはキービジュアルのぺこら！
On the back is the main visual illustration of Pekora!
この中に「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ、そしてジャケットを羽織ってうちに来たら、最高！
Wearing the \"You've gotta be kidding me...\" T-shirt under this jacket would be awesome!
お出かけにもちょうどいいぺこですね。
It's also great for going out!
そしてなんと、なんと、なんと！フルセットをご購入の方には
And what's more, what's more, what's more! For those who purchase the full set...
さらなる特典がございます！
there is an additional bonus!
こちら！
Behold!
数量限定でぺこらの直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる！
A limited edition postcard with Pekora's handwritten signature and foil-stamped message!
以上、ぜひ皆様、ジャンジャンバリバリゲットしてください！
So please, everyone, go ahead and grab yours!
うさだぺこらに夢と希望と未来を乗せまして
With Usada Pekora carrying your dreams, hopes, and future...
配信終了のお声が掛かりますまで
...until the announcement of the end of the stream...
一気にジャンジャンバリバリと、最終最後のお時間までご視聴くださいませ！
...please enjoy watching until the very end!
Ah 潮風に誘われて
Ah, invited by the sea breeze,
はしゃぐ声 波の音
with excited voices and the sound of waves,
近づいてゆく
getting closer.
Ah 高い空 白い雲
Ah, high sky, white clouds,
まぶしい海と恋の季節
the dazzling sea and the season of love.
日に焼けた
You, sun-kissed,
あなたが笑っていた
were laughing.
たくさんの光が キラキラ
Lots of light, sparkling.
コイするココロで 変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
With a heart in love, a lucky day is starting to change.
繋いだ手が ほら
Look, the hands we held
魔法にかかるよ
are under a magic spell.
笑ってばっかり
Just laughing,
ここは夏の国
this is the country of summer.
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
Ah 照らし出す 太陽が
Ah, the sun shining down
まぶしくて かき氷 イチゴえらんで
is dazzling, choosing strawberry shaved ice.
Ah 青い空 白い砂
Ah, blue sky, white sand,
コントラストなピンクのくち
the contrasting pink lips.
染まってく くちびる
Lips starting to stain,
照れ笑い
a shy smile.
誘ってるみたいで
As if tempting me,
ドキドキ
heart pounding.
コイするココロが スピードあげてく
The heart in love is increasing its speed.
My heart in love is speeding up...
見つめるヒトミが 大胆になるよ
The eyes staring are becoming bold.
言葉はいらない 今を感じたい
No words needed, I want to feel the now.
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
夕陽を映す海はオレンジ
The sea reflecting the sunset is orange,
二人のシルエット
the silhouette of the two of us.
足をさらう星の砂
Star sand that steals our feet...
そっと、ねえ連れてって遠くに
...softly, hey, take me far away.
コイするココロは もう止まらない！
The heart in love can no longer stop!
合わせた手のひら 合図を送るよ
Joined palms, sending a signal.
何もいらない ふたりだけの国
Nothing needed, a country for just the two of us.
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
コイするココロで 変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
With a heart in love, a lucky day begins to change.
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
The hands we connected, look, magic is cast on them.
笑ってばっかり ここは夏の国
Just laughing, this is the country of summer.
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
私のブランニュー・デイ！！！
My brand new day!!!
はい、みんな！
Hi everyone!
ぺこらのライブに来てくれてありぺこでした！
Thank you so much for coming to Pekora's live concert peko!
1曲目は「私バージョンアップ！」でした！
The first song was "Upgrade Me!".
1曲目、当てた人いますか？
Did anyone guess the first song?
何の曲が来るか、みんなたくさん考えてくれたと思うけど、
I'm sure you all thought a lot about what song was coming,
まずは1曲目は「私バージョンアップ！」でした！
but the first song was indeed "Upgrade Me!".
ということで、
And so,
今回も兎田ぺこらパチンコスロットライブ第3弾！
this is also the third Usada Pekora Pachinko Slot Live!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ということで、おいおいぺこちゃん、
With that said, "Hey, Peko-chan,
前回も前々回もパチンコスロットライブだったじゃん、
the last two were both pachinko slot lives, right?"
何で3回目をやるんだよ、
"Why are you doing it a third time?"
って思いましたよね？
is what you probably thought, right?
はい、私も3回目はやりすぎか、
Yes, I also wondered if a third time was too much,
さすがにやりすぎてるぺこなのかなって思ったんですけども、こちら見てください！
like maybe I'm overdoing it peko, but please look at this!
はい！兎田ぺこら7周年記念ライブということで、
Yes! This is the Usada Pekora 7th Anniversary Live, which means...
「7」なんです！
...it's "7"!
「7」と言ったらやるしかないよね？そうぺこだよね、
And when you think of "7", you've got to do it, right? That's right peko!
ということで、今回もやらせてください！
So, let me do it again this time!
めちゃめちゃね、良い曲たくさんあるぺこですので、
There are so many amazing songs peko,
絶対みんなも楽しんでもらえる、
so everyone will definitely enjoy it.
それだけは自信があるぺこなので、
I have absolute confidence in that peko,
ぜひともお楽しみに！そして、
so please look forward to it! And,
ハッシュタグのね、
Please use the hashtag,
「#兎田ぺこら7周年記念ライブ」もたくさん呟いてください！
"#UsadaPekora7thAnniversaryLive" and tweet a lot!
ということで、ここからはみんなお楽しみ of ゲストパート！
Now then, from here on is the guest part everyone's been waiting for!
今年はどんなお歌が来るのか、お楽しみに！
What kind of songs will we have this year? Look forward to it!
u3000兎神拳に二対一の戦いはない
In Bunny God Fist, there is no two-on-one battle!
覇王はこの拳王ただ一人！
There is only one Supreme King: this King of Fists!
北兎無双
[Title: Hokuto Musou]
DESTINY STAR
[Song: DESTINY STAR]
静寂の闇を 溶かす瞬き
Blinking that melts the silence of the darkness...
星座のstory 語りかければ
...if you speak to the story of the constellations.
それぞれの想い 弾かれるように
As if our respective feelings are released...
男達の旅は始まる
...the men's journey begins.
乾き果てて
In an era dried up...
ひび割れてく時代で
...and cracking...
たった一つの 信じるものを
...we chase after the single thing we believe in...
追い求めてく
...seeking it out.
輝くDestiny star 導かれて
Shining DESTINY STAR, guided by it...
野望の果てまで
...to the very end of our ambition.
譲れない願い 向き合う時
When we face our unyielding desires...
運命始まる
...our destiny begins.
(Go straight) 数えきれない
(Go straight) Countless...
(Far away) 悲しみを見つめ
(Far away) ...gazing at the sadness.
光放つ Destiny star
The shining DESTINY STAR...
いつも予言には 「答え」しかない
Prophecies always only contain the "answers"...
辿る道は 自分次第で
...but the path we take is up to us.
進むべき明日を 切り拓くよう
To carve out the tomorrow we must advance to...
男達は戦い続ける
...the men continue to fight.
命さえも 投げ出しても
Even if we have to throw away our lives...
構わない
...it doesn't matter.
そう思えるほど 守りたいもの
Because we found something we want to protect so much...
見つけたから
...ever since that day.
囁くDestiny star 迷い捨てて
Whispering DESTINY STAR, casting away all hesitation...
悪夢の果てまで
...to the very end of the nightmare.
一歩も引けない プライドから
From a pride that cannot back down even a single step...
火花が飛び散る
...sparks fly.
(Go straight) まだ遠くても
(Go straight) Even if it's still far away...
(Far away) その手を伸ばして
(Far away) ...reach out your hand...
つかまえてよ Destiny star
...and catch it, DESTINY STAR.
絆確かめ 未来の扉
Confirming our bond, we open...
開けて旅立つ
...the door to the future and set off.
輝くDestiny star 導かれて
Shining DESTINY STAR, guided by it...
野望の果てまで
...to the very end of our ambition.
譲れない願い 向き合う時
When we face our unyielding desires...
運命始まる
...our destiny begins.
(Go straight) 数えきれない
(Go straight) Countless...
(Far away) 悲しみを見つめ
(Far away) ...gazing at the sadness.
光放つ Destiny star
The shining DESTINY STAR...
Destiny star
チャンスぺこ！
This is my chance, peko!
激熱ぺこ！！！
Super hot, peko!!!
ここまでじゃ、ぺこの助。
This is the end for you, Pekonosuke!
恨みに歪んだ剣で ぺこーらは撃てぬぺこよ！
You can't defeat Pekora with a sword twisted by hatred, peko!
紅い雫滲む唇に
Crimson droplets blur on my lips,
ふわり嘆きの霧触れてゆく
...gently touched by the mist of mourning.
空に浮かぶ鏡美しく
The mirror floating beautifully in the sky...
遥か暗夜の彼方照らしてる
...illuminates the far-off distant night.
降り注ぐ数多の星に想い馳せて
Letting my thoughts wander to the countless stars pouring down,
しめやかに...
...quietly...
しめやかに深い絆の糸
Gently, the deep thread of our bond
強く強く結ぶ
Ties us strongly, so strongly
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Eyes shining in lapis lazuli
闇よりの使いに 閉ざされても
Even if they are sealed by messengers of darkness
繋いだ夢の橋 誰も奪えないから
No one can steal our connected bridge of dreams
無限の明日映して
Reflecting an infinite tomorrow
妖し光放つ鳴神に
Amidst the thunderclouds releasing a mysterious light
甘い言葉の蜜 薫り立つ
The sweet scent of honeyed words rises
密か黒い鼓翼 忍び寄る
Secretly, a dark wing stealthily approaches
心臓-鐘-が行き場求め 喘ぎ出す
The heart's bell groans, seeking a place to go
星霜の流れに隠す 歪んだ思惑
Twisted schemes hidden in the flow of time
艶やかに鋭い牙を剥く
Baring sharp, brilliant fangs
巡る巡る悲劇
Revolving, revolving tragedies
玉響に消えゆく 水泡のように
Disappearing in a fleeting moment like bubbles
儚い時 辿る運命なら
If destiny follows this fleeting time
曇りなき刃掲げ 清い詩紡ぐ
I will raise a cloudless blade and weave a pure song
譲れぬ未来のため
For the sake of an unyielding future
浅い眠り続く黎明に
In the dawn of continuing shallow sleep
独り祈り込めて 織り上げた
Offering a solitary prayer, I wove this together
涙 蒼い雲に刻まれて
My tears are engraved in the blue clouds
愛しあなたの影 追いかける
Chasing after your beloved shadow
憎しみの炎渦巻く この地上で
On this earth where flames of hatred swirl
汚れなき心 貫いてく
Piercing through with a pure heart
熱き熱き誓い
A burning, burning vow
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Eyes shining in lapis lazuli
闇よりの使いに 閉ざされても
Even if they are sealed by messengers of darkness
繋いだ夢の橋 悠久に綴りゆく
The connected bridge of dreams continues eternally
奏でる奇跡 きっと...
Playing a miracle, surely...
可能性の兎
[On-screen: The Rabbit of Possibility]
兎田ぺこら 変身まで
[On-screen: Usada Pekora: Until Transformation]
未来ある若者の芽を摘むな！
Don't nip the budding youth with a bright future!
後ろ向くなお前！前だけ見てろ人生！
Don't look back! Keep looking forward in life!
ぺこちゃんのことが、大好きです
I love you, Peko-chan.
覚醒
[On-screen: Awakening]
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
時の鼓動がまだ響く間
While the heartbeat of time still echoes
...間
...still echo,
裸の言葉胸に閉じ込めた
I hid those naked words deep in my chest.
記憶の色が滲み始める
The colors of my memory have begun to fade
破れた世界の隅で
in the corner of a broken world.
何も求めずにただ抱き寄せる
I don't want anything but to hold you,
今の僕にはそれしか出来ない
right now that's all I can do.
震えた強がりでもプライドに見える
Trembling beneath feigned courage that only looks like pride,
逸れた子供のように
like a lost child.
最後の声さえも
Even my last words
風がさまようせいで消された
will be lost in the roaming winds.
月に手を向けたまま
As I turned my hands to the moon,
君は空の星に消えた
you vanished into the stars.
「側にいて」と抱きしめても
Even if I hold you and say "Stay by my side,"
もう二度と聞こえない君の歌声は
I won't hear your singing voice again.
降り注いだ雨のサイレン
The siren of a pouring rain,
僕の代わりに今この空が泣き続ける
instead of me, the cosmos keeps on crying.
これまで踏みつけてきた教えを
Even if I gather up the teachings I've trampled on until now
今掻き集めこの胸に当てても
and press them against my chest,
救い求め歌うようなお遊戯に見える
it looks like a game where I'm using my song to ask for salvation
物語る大人のように
like adults telling legends.
言葉に寄り添うだけの
I don't need a love of the skies and guidance
空の愛と導きはいらない
that just clings to words.
飾られた祈りでは
In this decorated prayer,
明日の手懸かりに触れない
I can't feel the next step to tomorrow.
いつか君に届くはずの
One day it will surely reach you,
名も無き幼い詩が描くままを
this unadorned, nameless poem of my youth.
忘れたいよ 一度だけ
I want to forget it just once.
眠れぬ悲しみがその詩を抱きしめてる
The pain of sleepless nights is holding that poem.
Freezing cold shatters my sorrow
And scorching sand puts it together again
投げ捨てられる正しさなら
If it's a kind of correctness that can be thrown away,
消える事ない間違いの方が良い
then it's better to have mistakes that will never disappear.
臆病に隠してた声を今
If I expose the shyness I've hidden in my voice,
この手でもう一度晒せば良い
once more with my own hands...
掴む軌道も咲く光も
Even the trajectory I grasped and the light that bloomed
乾いた心のせいでモノクロに見えた
looked monochrome due to my dried-out heart.
忘れないよ 今日の景色を
I won't forget the scenery of today.
ありふれた願いが足元を照らしてくれる
This ordinary wish will light the path before my feet.
Please hear me / I want to tell you
Please sing to me / I wanna hear your voice
ふう… ぺこーら一体どうなったぺこ…？
Whew... Pekora... what on earth happened, peko...?
一匹残らず…
I'll wipe out every single one of them...
喰らってやる！
I will devour you!
Clawing inside my head
Shredding my self-control
It's getting close to the edge
I'm breaking down
Fragmented memories are glitching in my head
Stuck in a moment and it's burning up, bright red
A roaring howl disappears into the night
My soul is here to stay, wow wow wow wow
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity, it's changing me
My heartbeat is racing so fast
Unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now, I'm just getting started
Hey now
This ain't who I am
Obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now
Look what I've become
Obey now to me!
Your hopes gonna turn to fear
When I scream
Corrosive voices laugh and whisper in my head
Tried to ignore 'em but they're calling for a bloodshed
I'm like a puppet, someone's pulling all the strings
Drowning in misery, I can't get out!
Breakout this rusted gate
Search and eradicate
Burning the hate from within
Ready to dominate
It's time to liberate
The chaos inside of him, wow wow wow wow
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity, straining me
My heartbeat is racing so fast
Unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now, I'm just getting started
Hey now
This ain't who I am
Obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now
Look what I've become
Obey now to me!
Your hopes gonna turn to fear
When I scream
Woah...
ハラペコチャレンジ！
Harapeko Challenge!
負けないぺこ！
I won't lose, peko!
とうっ！
Toh!
ハラペコドライブ！
Harapeko Drive!
伝説の朝に
On that morning of legend...
誓った言葉
...the words we pledged...
分かち合う声に
...let the miracle illuminate...
奇跡よ照らせ
...our shared voices.
革命を
Revolution...
Let's shout!
革命を
Revolution...
Let's shout!
革命デュアリズム
[Revolution Dualism]
風の舞うヒカリの空
Through the sky of light where the wind dances...
吹き抜けぬ残響
...the echo blows through.
この右手と
This right hand and...
この左手
...this left hand...
何を求める？
...what do they wish for?
魂のカタルシスに
Our longing emotions...
焦がれた感情を
...for the soul's catharsis.
重ね合えば
If we overlap them...
繋ぎ合えば
...if we connect them...
伝うのか？
...will the message come through?
運命に委ね
Surrendered to destiny...
流れるままに
...going with the flow...
変わらぬビジョンじゃ
...an unchanging vision...
面白くない
...is not interesting!
沸騰せよ
Boil away...
血液のレイヴ
...rave of blood!
交錯する
Intersecting...
プラズマのように
...like plasma!
革命のデュアリズム
Revolution's dualism...
さあ始めよう
...now, let's begin!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
The telepathic roar of life...
届いていますか？
...does it reach where you are?
化学反応 愛が伝承
This chemical reaction of love is an epic.
ついて来い 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of the dream!
どんなロードだって
No matter what path of life...
いつかは交じり合う
...it will merge together someday.
その日 君は
When that day comes, you...
ジャッジメントする
...will pass the judgement.
革命を
Let's shout!
プラスマイナスが0の
A decent tuning...
悪くはないチューニング
...balanced perfectly at zero.
キスみたいにクラックした
Like a kiss, it has cracked into my system...
色褪せないドリーム
...a forever-colorful dream.
カミサマは希望与え
The gods grant us hope...
痛みを暈して
...obscuring the pain.
何を守り
What do I protect?
何を信じ
What do I believe?
生きろと云う？
In your words, how should I live?
未来へのドアは
The door to the future...
コイントスさ
...is the toss of a coin.
残酷を選べ
Choose cruelty...
暁の君
...you of the daybreak!
虹の架かる
I'll show you a flight...
見たことない|絶景のフライト
...above a stunning view...
絶景のフライト
...crossing the rainbow as you've never seen.
教えてやる
I will show you!
覚醒の
Awakening's...
デュアリズム
...dualism...
さあ飛び込もう
...now, let's fly in!
百花繚乱
Emerging legends...
共振る衝動
...howling impulse...
火花を散らして
...send the sparks flying!
胸のブレイブを叩く鼓動
The beats, pounding out your heart's bravery...
どこまでいけるのか？
...how far can we go?
変わらない「ナニカ」で
With "something" that has never changed...
何度信頼した？
...how many times have you trusted?
そして君は
And then you...
また物語に出会う
...once again meet a love, a story.
Just trust my heart
Just feel my heart
...hold you...
誇り高き愛の結晶
Once you have the crystals of prideful love...
握りしめたら
...tight in your grasp...
迎えにゆくから
...I'll go out to meet you.
刹那から一生さえ
The journey from a moment to our whole lives...
すべて見せてきた
...was enough to show me everything.
君への Love song
A love song to you...
Break out!
鎖千切って
Snap apart your chains!
独立セヨ
Declare your independence!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
Does the telepathic roar of life...
届いていますか？
...reach where you are?
化学反応 愛が伝承
This chemical reaction of love is an epic.
ついて来い 夢の果て規定
Follow me to the end of the dream!
どんなロードだって
All paths of life...
いつかは交じり合う
...will merge together someday.
その日 君は
When that day comes, you...
ジャッジメントする
...will pass the judgement.
革命を
Revolution...
Let's shout!
革命を
Revolution...
Let's shout!
ヘブンズペコラッシュ突入ぺこ！
Entering Heaven's Peko Rush, peko!
BARを撃ち抜け！
Shoot through the BAR!
当たれー！
Please hit!
スーパーヘブンズペコラッシュ突入ぺこ！
Entering Super Heaven's Pekorush, peko!
I have a big gun
I took it from my Lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
Been burned in hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
from when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Have no prayer
So, I keep the gun with me
For my safety
I'll do it with no sweat
They mean business
No time for sissy pig
Queen of ocean
Sing "the Volga" to you
No need to think about it
You do it or you die
Those aren't tears
Don't let it trick on you
I am hard as steel
Get out of my way
Pay back all at once
Suck away the tender part
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world's
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world's
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
みなさん
Everyone...
え〜...
Um...
発表があります！
I have an announcement!
大チャンス！
Big chance!
P K R 48!
ぺこらんだむぶれいんは 叫んじゃえば
If you just scream out "Pekorandom Brain!"
時短だ！不意に事態変更！
It's rush time! A sudden change of plans!
抱いてこう この「ありがとう」
Let's embrace this gratitude
笑えないような未来は笑え
Smile even through a smile-less future!
おだぶつぺこ！
You're dead, peko!
聞きたくない！いいわけバニー
I don't wanna hear it! Excuses Bunny
時短だの言うてうだうだ
Saying it's rush time and complaining
さん ファニファニ ダニダニマシーナ 楽しい どっちどっちが好きなのよ
Three, funny funny, dummy dummy machine, fun, which, which one do you like?
すぐ近くなのに 離れて感じる
Even though we are so close, I feel the distance.
君はバスの2つ前の席
You are two seats ahead of me on the bus.
声をかけるには ちょっと恥ずかしい
It's a little embarrassing to call out to you.
何度も恋をしても 慣れないね
No matter how many times I fall in love, I don't get used to it.
カーブ曲がり 身体が傾く時
When the bus curves and my body leans,
その方向は同じさ
we are headed in the same direction.
君に重力シンパシー
I have a gravity of sympathy for you.
何も話せなくても
Even if I can't say anything,
確かに今僕らは ひとつになる
I am sure that we are now becoming one.
君に重力シンパシー
I have a gravity of sympathy for you.
後ろ気づかなくても
Even if you don't realize that I am behind you,
わかり合える日が来るよ
the day will come when we can understand each other.
窓が曇るほど 乗客は多く
The windows fog up as the passengers increase,
君の顔が陰で見えなくなる
and your face becomes obscured in the shadow.
喋るその声に 耳を傾けて
Listening carefully to your voice,
僕は胸の奥をときめかせた
my heart beats deeply within my chest.
バスが急に スピード上げた瞬間
At the moment the bus suddenly speeds up,
みんな一緒に仰け反った
we all lean backward together.
愛は重力フレンズ
Love is a gravity friend.
そこにいるそれだけで
Just by being there,
2人はそう地球を共有する
we are sharing the Earth together.
愛は重力フレンズ
Love is a gravity friend.
存在認知されてなくても
Even if you don't recognize my existence,
そのベクトル進めばいい
it's fine if we continue along that vector.
君に重力シンパシー
I have a gravity of sympathy for you.
何も話せなくても
Even if I can't say anything,
確かに今僕らは ひとつになる
I am sure that we are now becoming one.
君に重力シンパシー
I have a gravity of sympathy for you.
いつか同じ重さで
Someday, with the same weight,
愛について想うだろう
you will think of love.
みんな盛り上がっていくぺこよ！
Everyone, let's get hyped, peko!
いくよー！
Here we go!
ラヴィラヴィちいさなビットに デッカイアイを交信中
Lovi-lovi, broadcasting huge love on a tiny bit
ちょっと沼っても許してね いったって愛は非効率
Forgive me if I get a bit hooked, after all, love is inefficient
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom
一度きりの物語
A once-in-a-lifetime story
ヤマトナデシコ いつだって
Yamato Nadeshiko, always
時代を彩る Dreamer
A Dreamer coloring the era
A dreamer coloring the era...
無限の彼方へ
...to the ends of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はい！
All together! Yes!
乙女フェスティバル
[Title: Otome Festival]
恋に焦がれてドキドキ
My heart pounds with yearning love,
いじわるなんてイヤイヤ
and being mean is a big no-no!
とびっきりのスマイルで
With an extraordinary smile,
あなたを連れてってあげる
I will take you with me.
惹かれちゃうのは運命
Getting drawn to you is fate,
あれもこれも抱きしめてあげる
so I will embrace each and every thing.
選ぶ道に誇りあれ
May there be pride in the path you choose!
進めば 輝く未来
If we move forward, a bright future awaits.
乙女心 いつだってフェスティバル
A girl's heart is always a festival!
きらめいて トキメキ届けたい 今すぐに
I want to sparkle and deliver my excitement to you right now!
高く高く そびえ立つ壁も
No matter how high the towering wall stands,
やがて超えてくイメージだけで Let's Go! Let's Go!
just imagining crossing it will carry us! Let's Go! Let's Go!
花が咲く 夢が咲く 一度きりの物語
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom, in this once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行く運命だから やるだけやるんです
Since they are destined to scatter eventually, we must do all we can!
笑いましょう 声高く 明日の自分に届けたい
Let's laugh out loud, wishing to reach our future selves!
ヤマトナデシコ いつだって
The Yamato Nadeshiko, always and forever,
時代を彩る Dreamer
a dreamer coloring the era...
無限の彼方へ
...to the ends of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はい！
All together! Yes!
ワガママだっていいでしょ？
It's okay to be a little selfish, right?
可愛いって言ってなでなで
Tell me I'm cute and pat my head!
お気に入りのスカートで
Wearing my favorite skirt,
あなたに飛び込んでみたい
I want to dive right to you!
夢見るだけじゃ足りない
Just dreaming is not enough,
決める時は迷わず行きましょ
so when it's time to decide, let's go without hesitation!
その手で掴む時まで
Until the moment you grasp it with your hands,
未来へ加速して行こう
let's keep accelerating toward the future!
Destiny いつか あなたと一緒に
Destiny... Someday, together with you,
永遠に触れてみたい ずっと憧れです
I want to touch eternity; I've always longed for it.
涙はらり こぼれ落ちる日も
Even on days when tears softly fall,
本気の愛で振り向かせたい Going! Going!
I'll make you look my way with genuine love! Going! Going!
花と舞い 夢と生き 重なり合う物語
Dancing with flowers, living with dreams, our overlapping stories.
諦めなんて似合わないから やるしかないでしょ
Giving up doesn't suit us, so we have no choice but to do it!
期待から希望へと 願いを鳴り響かせて
From expectation to hope, let our wishes resound!
ヤマトナデシコ きらめいて
The Yamato Nadeshiko, shining bright,
高鳴りを超える Future Soldier
surpassing the throbbing heartbeat, a Future Soldier!
奇跡を信じて
Believing in miracles...
ご一緒に！ はい！
All together! Yes!
隠しきれない熱い想いと 今を走れ走れ
With hot feelings we can't hide, run through the present!
負けない誓い一緒に掲げて行こう
Let's raise our undefeated vow together and march on!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う 予感に誘われ
Drawn by the premonition, dancing elegantly with this and that,
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
passion burns as we take flight!
無邪気なままじゃいられない
I can't just stay innocent forever,
切り開いて見つけたいな
I want to carve out my path and find it...
本当も嘘もない私になって
becoming my true self, free from truths or lies!
花が咲く 夢が咲く 一度きりの物語
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom, in this once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行く運命だから やるだけやるんです
Since they are destined to scatter eventually, we must do all we can!
笑いましょう 声高く 明日の自分に届けたい
Let's laugh out loud, wishing to reach our future selves!
ヤマトナデシコ いつだって
The Yamato Nadeshiko, always and forever,
時代を彩る Dreamer
a dreamer coloring the era...
無限の彼方へ
...to the ends of infinity!
ご一緒に！ はい！
All together! Yes!
隠しきれない熱い想いと 今を走れ走れ
With hot feelings we can't hide, run through the present!
負けない誓い一緒に掲げて行こう
Let's raise our undefeated vow together and march on!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う 予感に誘われ
Drawn by the premonition, dancing elegantly with this and that,
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
passion burns as we take flight!
大好きな 歌の中なら
If it's inside my favorite song...
声にいでて いいのぺこ
it's fine to speak up, peko!
思い出が強さになった
Memories became strength.
君ならば歌えるぺこ
If it's you, you can sing, peko!
今日という過去が生まれて
The past called "today" is born...
未来にはどうしたいか？ 描くんだ
What do you want to do in the future? Draw it!
心から ぺこらから
From the heart, from Pekora...
「ありがとう」歌ってあげたいんだ
I want to sing "Thank you" to you.
RADIANT FORCE
始まる歌
Start the song,
始まる鼓動
start the heartbeat,
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Let the sound of hope ring out!
「生きる事」を
"Don't give up on living,"
諦めないと
show it!
示せ
Show it!
熱き夢の
Of a passionate dream,
幕開けを
the curtain rise!
風よ
Wind!
この奇跡に嘘はない
There are no lies in this miracle!
その手は
What is that hand for,
何を掴むためにある？
to grab hold of?
多分 待つだけじゃ叶わない
Probably just waiting won't make it come true.
その手は
What is that hand for,
何を守るためにある？
to protect?
伝う 熱は
The heat that is passed on
明日を輝かす種火に
will become the spark to make tomorrow shine!
さあ 新時代へ 引き金を引こう
Come, let's pull the trigger to the new era,
伝説の未来へとカウントダウン
Countdown to the legendary future.
羽ばたきは 一人じゃない
Flapping wings are not alone.
過去を 超えた 先に
Beyond the past we have surpassed,
創るべき歴史が
The history that should be created
咲き燃えてる
is blooming and burning!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Bond, heart, bundled into one,
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Let the sound of hope ring out!
「信ず事」を諦めないと
"Don't give up on believing,"
唄え
sing it!
可能性に
There is no zero
ゼロはない
in possibility!
飛べよ
Fly,
この奇跡に
let there be light
光あれ
in this miracle!
切り裂けまだ見ぬ日に行くために
Tear it open, to go to days we have not yet seen,
不可能なんて何一つない
There is no such thing as impossible.
こんなに心強いことはない
There is nothing as heartening as this.
絶対
Absolutely,
absolutely,
絶対
信じ合いぶっちぎる
believe in each other and break through!
例え闇に吸い込まれそうになって
Even if it seems like you'll be sucked into the darkness,
涙さえも血に濡れて苦しくっても
Even if your tears are soaked in blood and it's painful,
帰る場所が待っている
The place to return to is waiting.
集え
Gather,
守れ
protect,
契れ
pledge,
勇気の結晶が
The crystal of courage
奇跡なんだ
is a miracle!
願い、祈り、すべてを背負い
Wish, prayer, carrying it all on your back,
本気を超えた本気の唄
A song of earnestness that exceeds earnestness!
痛みなんて何も怖くない
Nothing like pain is scary,
滾れ
Boil,
沸騰せよ
let it boil,
このカラダ
this body!
翳せ
Hold it up,
さあ
come,
闇夜に稲妻を
lightning in the dark night!
出会い笑い合いそして泣きじゃくり
Meeting, laughing together, and then sobbing,
命の炎も一緒に燃やして
Burning the flame of life together too,
五感の全部が叫ぶ
All five senses scream,
愛と
As much as
呼べる
can be called
程の
love,
眩しく煌めいた
The proof of a friend
友の証
that shines dazzlingly!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Bond, heart, bundled into one,
響き鳴り渡れ 希望の音
Resonate and ring out, sound of hope
「信ずる事」を諦めないと
Saying, "I won't give up on believing"
唄え
Sing!
可能性に
To the possibilities,
ゼロはない
there is no zero.
飛べよ
Fly!
この
Into this
奇跡に
miracle,
光あれ
let there be light!
コムハワリゾートへようこそ！
Welcome to Comhwa Resort!
わし、わし、わし、わし、わしが行く！
I-I-I-I-I'm going!
コムハワリゾートとは、わしのことだ！
Comhwa Resort is all about me!
みんな、ライブを観てくれてありぺこ！
Everyone, thank you so much for watching the live show, aripeko!
この後、10時15分よりメンバー限定アンコールLIVEがあるぺこ！
After this, starting at 10:15 PM, we have a member-only encore live show, peko!
まだまだぺこらの新衣装見たいぺこだよね？
You still want to see more of Pekora's new outfit, right?
ぺこらも歌も歌いたいし、みんなに新衣装もっと見てほしい！
Pekora wants to sing more, and I want everyone to see my outfit even more!
なので是非とも遊びに来てぺこ！
So please come and hang out with me, peko!
そして、グッズのおさらいです！
And now, let's review the merchandise!
1つ目は、アクリルパネル！
First up is the acrylic panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishの一伊那尓栖ちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
This one was actually illustrated by Ninomae Ina'nis from Hololive English!
ありがとう、イナ！本当に可愛いぺこーら、かっこいいしオシャレだし！
Thank you, Ina! It's a super cute, cool, and stylish Pekora!
是非ともゲットしてみてぺこな！
Please make sure to get one, peko!
2つ目は、こちら！
Second is this one!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Random acrylic keyholders!
イラストは、まむえり先生に描いてもらいました！
The illustrations were drawn by Mamueri-sensei!
いや、最高なキーホルダー来ました、こちら！
Wow, these are the absolute best keyholders right here!
「7」をやっぱり3つ揃えたいのが人間のサガなのかな？
I guess it's human nature to want to get three '7's aligned?
どう、ぺこなんでしょうか？
What do you think, peko?
是非とも何が届くか、お楽しみに！
Please look forward to finding out which one you get!
そして3つ目は、
And thirdly...
ぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
A 'Uso peko desho...' T-shirt handwritten by Pekora!
大人気の直筆Tシャツ「うそぺこでしょ」出ました！
The super popular handwritten T-shirt 'You're lying, peko?!' is here!
部屋着にね、ぴったりだと思うぺこだし、ま、
I think it's absolutely perfect for loungewear, and...
「うそぺこでしょ」Tシャツで是非とも外に出かけるのも全然アリぺこだと思うので、
it's also totally fine to wear the 'Uso peko' T-shirt when going out!
是非チェックしてみてください！
So please check it out!
そして4つ目は、
And fourthly...
トラックジャケット！
The track jacket!
キービジュアルのぺこらが着ているのと同じぺこ！
It's the exact same one Pekora is wearing in the key visual, peko!
是非ともぺこらとお揃いで着ませんか？
Won't you match outfits with Pekora?
かっこいいしね、なんかオシャレじゃない？
It looks cool and pretty stylish, don't you think?
こちらもね、コンビニ行くときでもいいし、それとも
You can wear it to go to the convenience store, or
遊びに行くときでもいい、部屋着にしてもいい！
wear it when going out, or even as loungewear!
もうね、たくさん着てもらえたら嬉しいぺこなんで、要チェックな！
I'd be so happy if you wear it a lot, so check it out!
そして、こちらのグッズフルセットでご購入いただきますと、
And if you purchase the full merchandise set...
数量限定で、ぺこらの直筆サイン＆複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる！
you will receive a postcard with my handwritten signature and printed message in limited quantities!
是非ともお手にとってください！
Please make sure to get your hands on it!
ビッビッビッ！ばっばっばっばっばっ！うりゃりゃりゃりゃりゃりゃ！
Bip-bip-bip! Bap-bap-bap-bap-bap! Uryaryaryaryarya!
ハリー！最高だ！
Hurry! This is awesome!
待ていましたこの瞬間！
I've been waiting for this moment!
いいですいいですめちゃいいです！
It's good! It's so good!
はっはっはっはっ！
Hahahaha!
おいえー！おいえー！
Oi-yea! Oi-yea!
きたきたきたきたきた！
Here it comes, here it comes!
うー、さばら！
Woo, sabara!
あげあげ！ハリケーン！
Pump it up! Hurricane!
くるのかい？消えてしまうのか？
Is it coming? Is it going to disappear?
ゴー！ゴー！
Go! Go!